Slava Melnik

+7-929-111-11-11 | blank@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/slavamel | github.com/Slavamel

Summary

Creative and self-starting web developer with 5+ years experience building stable enterprise websites and apps in fast-paced, collaborative environments. I'm passionate about learning and using modern technologies, and I'm always think about the end user and how I can improve my work to do it better and more efficiently.

EXPERIENCE

DHL Express

Moscow, Russia

Full-Stack Developer

May 2017 - Present

- Developed and supported enterprise web applications from the ground up, including code and database architecture.
- Set up and maintained CI/CD via TeamCity.
- Taught myself Angular 2 and .NET Core frameworks, as well as mentoring a team through presentations about those frameworks.
- Organized team meetups, where we would share our knowledge throughout the team and discuss new technologies, frameworks, best practices etc
- Mentored junior developers and helped newcomers.
- Participated voluntarily in organised company events and activities, such as joining in on charity events and conducting various trainings as a facilitator.

DHL Express

Moscow, Russia

 $Application\ Support\ Specialist$

March 2015 - May 2017

- Improved technical communication skills.
- Increased my knowledge about how users see an application, how they interact with it.
- Developed a one page website by teaching myself HTML, CSS, JS, with a user friendly interface that automates configuration files generation. I saw an opportunity and a challenge to automate a part of my work and I did it in my free time. That accomplishment impact to the whole department and helped us save a lot of time. And my colleagues are still using it.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: TypeScript / JavaScript / C# / SQL

Frameworks and Libraries: Angular / Angular Material / RxJs / SCSS / Webpack / .NET Framework / .NET Core / Entity Framework / Autofac

Languages: English (Upper-Intermediate B2), Ukrainian (Advanced), Russian (Native)

EDUCATION

Russian New University

Moscow

Bachelor of Applied Computer Science in Economy

2006-2011